A Guide to the Thomas Inge papers, 1879-2001
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
Thomas Inge papers 1879-2001
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
M 82: 84-Sep-22; 90-Apr-38; 90-Jul-91
This collection is 45.64 linear feet.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
This collection is open to research.
Acquisitions Information
In February 1975, Dr. Inge donated a collection of his papers on the comic arts and materials related to American literature. The typescript copies of Ellen Glasgow: Centennial Essays and Frontier Humor were given by Inge in July, 1976. In August, 1976, the galley's for the Glasgow book were added to the collection. In 1984, a collection of comic books were given by Sarah Abrams through Dr. Inge. In 1988, Dr. Inge gave on deposit a large amount of comic art related materials. Additions to these deposits was began 1990 and have continued on a semi-annual basis.
Biographical/Historical Information
"M. Thomas Inge, Ph.D. is the Robert Emory Blackwell Professor of English and the Humanities at Randolph-Macon College in Ashland, Virginia. A native of Newport News, Virginia, he received his B.A. degree in English and Spanish from Randolph-Macon College in 1959 and his M.A. and Ph.D. degrees in English and American literature from Vanderbilt University in 1960 and 1964 respectively. After teaching at Vanderbilt University, he became a member of the Department of American Thought and Language at Michigan State University from 1964 to 1969, when he joined the Department of English at Virginia Commonwealth University in Richmond. He served as Chair of the department from 1974 to 1980 and then was Head of the Department of English at Clemson University in South Carolina. From 1982 to 1984, he was appointed Resident Scholar in American Studies by the U.S. Information Agency in Washington.
As a senior Fulbright Lecturer, Inge has taught at the University of Salamanca in Spain (1967-68) and at three institutions in Buenos Aires, Argentina (1971). On a third Fulbright appointment in 1979, he offered courses on American humor and literary regionalism at Moscow State University in the Soviet Union. As resident Scholar with USIA, he consulted and lectured abroad in eighteen countries, including France, Italy, Portugal, Japan, New Zealand, Thailand, Indonesia, Malaysia, and the People's Republic of China. More recently, he has lectured in Poland, Austria, Hungary, Romania, Finland, Denmark, England, Germany, and the Czech Republic. At the invitation of the Gorky Institute, he returned to the Soviet Union to participate in conferences on Sholokhov and Faulkner and the works of Eudora Welty. He has led travel-study courses to the Soviet Union in 1988 and China in 1989, and in 1994 he taught at Charles University in Prague on a fourth Fulbright lectureship.
Among others, Inge teaches courses in American humor and satire and is the author or editor of over fifty books. His three-volume Handbook of American Popular Culture was cited by the American Library Association as an outstanding reference work in 1979 and was issued in a revised and expanded edition in 1989. In addition to his continuing interests in literature, Inge is also engaged in research on the history and development of American comic art, which resulted in his book "Comics as Culture."
More recent publications include "Anything Can Happen in a Comic Strip," a study of self-referentiality in the comics, and "Charles M. Schulz: Conversations, a collection of interviews with the creator of Peanuts," the first in a series of such collections for which Inge is serving as the general editor for the University Press of Mississippi. Works in progress include books on the relations between American literature and the comics and the adaptation process in the films of Walt Disney."
This biography is from the website Witty World: International Cartoon Center at http://www.wittyworld.com/bios/bioinge.html. It was accessed on September 11, 2002.
Scope and Content Information
This collection is composed of materials collected by Dr. Inge relating to his academic studies of the comic arts, popular culture, and American literature. The bulk of the collection is dated from the 1950s onward and is made up of many unique items collected by Inge covering the history of the comic arts. It includes a large collection of published and unpublished materials and ephemera items relating to the comic arts. Manuscripts by Inge and other writers are also included. The collection contains correspondence with a number of noted artists and writers, including Art Spieglman, Mort Walker, Bruce Duncan, and Harold Foster, and comic arts scholars. The collection includes advertisements, fan club materials, posters, art prints, animation cells, comic strip and comic book samples, comic and animation character drinking glasses, numerous buttons, records, and various other collectable items. Other materials incorporate Inge's interests in American literature and include typescript copies of the Ellen Glasgow Newsletter and Frontier Home, copies of literary journals, numerous publications, and correspondence. The collection also contains items of Dr. Inge's own personal collection of materials ranging from his grade school papers and school yearbooks to an autograph scrapbook and EC Fan Club dating from the 1950s.
The collection is highlighted by a very large collection of reference journals including fanzines, newsletters, journals, and numerous other periodicals related to the comic arts. These periodical titles focus on the history and art of comic books and comic strips, cartoonists, comic book and comic strip characters, animation, and other aspects of the comic arts and popular culture. These materials, and the hundreds of comic books and reference books donated by Dr. Inge, have been incorporated into their own individual collections.
Organization
Series I - Comic Arts. Sub-series A - Correspondence (1908-2002), Sub-series B - Published and Unpublished Works by Inge (1962-2002), Sub-series C - Published and Unpublished Works by Others (1879-1995), Sub-series D - Other Comic Related Items (1972-2001), Sub-series E - Oversized Items (1894-2001).
Series II - Other Literary Materials and Personal Items. Sub-series A - Ellen Glasgow (1971-1976), Sub-series B - Personal Items (1915-2000), Sub-series C - Photographs (1957-1975).
Separated Material
Books and other materials have been integrated into the department collection. Comic books have been integrated into the comic book collection.
Contents List
- Series I - Comic Arts
  - Sub-series A - Correspondence
    - Animation, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Barker, Kenneth 1977 - 1979 (Box 1)
    - Bodé Collectors, The, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Cartoon Art Museum, undated, 1988, 1998, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Cartoon Art Museum Invitations, undated, 1989, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Cartoonist undated, 1972, 1975 - 1976, 1983, 1988, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Comic Research Library, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Copyright Office, 1975 (Box 1)
    - DC Comics, undated, 1977, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Dealers, 1977, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Dobbins, L. C., undated, 1974, 1977 - 1978 (Box 1)
    - Duncan, Bruce, undated, 1982 - 1984, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Dyna Pubs, 1980 (Box 1)
    - E. C. Comics Pen-Pals, 1953 - 1954 (Box 1)
    - Elias, Sidney, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Eloit, Jan, 1998 (Box 1)
    - European Cartoonist, undated, 1973 - 1974 (Box 1)
    - Fanzines, 1972 - 1974, 1977, 1980, 1982, 1985, 1989 - 1990, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Foreign Publishers, 1973, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Forum for Contemporary History 1 of 2, undated, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Forum for Contemporary History 2 of 2, 1972 - 1973 (Box 1)
    - Funnies Paper, The, 1999 - 2000 (Box 1)
    - Geerdes, Clay, undated, 1975, 1980 - 1981 (Box 1)
    - Harvey, R. C., 1991 (Box 1)
    - Hinds Jr., Harold, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Invitations, undated, 1979, 1993 - 1994, 1996 (Box 1)
    - International Museum of Cartoon Art, 1994 - 1996, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Jaeger, Sharon, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Jonathan David Publishers, Inc., undated, 1975, 1977 - 1978 (Box 1)
    - Journal of Popular Culture- Erling Holtzmark, undated, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Journal of Popular Culture- Lawrence Mintz, undated, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Journal of Popular Culture- Miscellaneous, undated, 1976 - 1980 (Box 1)
    - Journal of Popular Culture- Daniel Mishken, 1978 - 1979 (Box 1)
    - Journal of Popular Culture- Thomas Pendleton, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Kirch, Shelby, undated (Box 1)
    - Lawrence Scripps Wilkenson Collection of Toys, undated, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Leavitt, Craig, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Magazines, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Marvel Comics Group, undated (Box 1)
    - Mattox, Guy Douglas, undated, 1975, 1977 - 1981 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous A - L, 1974 - 1982, 1984, 1986, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous M- Z, 1972, 1975, 1977 - 1983, 1985, 1990, 1991, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Christmas Cards, undated, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Greeting Cards, undated (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Postcards, undated, 1981, 1986, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Museum of Cartoon Art, undated, 1975, 1977, 1979, 1980, 1983, 1987, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Museum of Cartoon Art Invitations, 1977, 1980, 1983, 1987, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Museums 1972, 1986, 1998, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Newspapers, 1975, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Organizations, undated, 1974, 1976, 1977, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Plas, Wim Vander, 1980, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Publishers, undated, 1971 - 1978, 1980 - 1981, 1996, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Publisher Form Letter, undated (Box 1)
    - Randolph Macon College Yearbook Project, undated, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Randolph Macon College Yearbook Project - Bob Hope, undated (Box 1)
    - Randolph Macon College Yearbook Project - Hank Ketcham, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Randolph Macon College Yearbook Project - Harold Foster, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Randolph Macon College Yearbook Project - Mickey Mantle, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Randolph Macon College Yearbook Project - Milton Caniff, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Richard, Ted, 1976 - 1977, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Seibel, Fred O., 1951 (Box 1)
    - Spiegelman, Art, undated, 1980 (Box 1)
    - St. Martin's Press, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Walker, Mort, undated (Box 1)
    - Walt Disney Educational Media Company, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Will Eisner Studios, Inc., 1975 - 1976, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Words and Pictures Museum, undated, 1994 - 1996, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Sub-series B - Published and Unpublished Works by Inge
    - Articles:
      - "American Comic Art: A Bibliographic Guide," undated, 1976 (Box 2)
      - "An American Novel of Ideas," 1967 (Box 2)
      - "Art and Allegory in Truman Capote's In Cold Blood" with notes and correspondence, undated, 1966, 1968 (Box 2)
      - "A Chronology of the Development of the American Comic Book," 1975 (Box 2)
      - "Comic Book: An American Phenomenon, The," undated (Box 2)
      - "Comics and American Language, The" 1976 (Box 2)
      - "Comics as Culture," 1975 (Box 2)
      - "Dr. Rappaccini's Noble Experiment," 1973 (Box 2)
      - "Importance of the American Comics, The" and notes, undated (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous Richmond Times Dispatch Sunday Book Reviews, 1979 (Box 2)
      - "Politics in the Comics," 1979 (Box 2)
      - "Why Study the Comics," undated (Box 2)
    - Editor:
      - American Literary Scholarship, 1970-1974 (Box 2)
    - Exhibition:
      - "The American Comic Strip: Its History and Development," undated (Box 2)
      - {Photographs and negatives accompanying this exhibition have been moved to Series II Sub-Series - C - Photographs} (Box 2)
      - "Cavalcade of American Comics, The", 1974-1975 (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2)
    - Lecture:
      - "A Chronology of the Development of the American Comic Book," undated, 1974 (Box 2)
      - "Comics as Culture, drafts and discussion," undated (Box 2)
      - "A History of American Comic Art," 1973 (Box 2)
    - Manuscripts:
      - American Reader, The: American Literary Thought Curriculum, undated, 1965 (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Author Headnotes, undated (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Author Headnotes and Section Introductions, edited, undated (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Comments, undated, 1967, 1971 (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Contracts and Reprint Permissions, undated 1966, 1969,1970 (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Correspondence, undated, 1966 - 1967 (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Correspondence, 1968 - 1970 (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Correspondence, 1971 - 1973 (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Editor's Preface, undated (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Galley Proofs, undated (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Manuscript 1 of 2, undated, 1970-1972 (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Manuscript, 2 of 2, undated, 1973 (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Manuscript, edited, undated (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Outlines, undated (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Personal notebook, undated (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Publisher Guidelines, undated, 1962, 1966 (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Research Materials, (4 folders), undated (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Sample Preface and Working Assumptions, undated, 1966 (Box 2)
      - American Reader, The: Section Introductions, undated (Box 2)
      - An American Reader: The Seventeenth and Eighteenth Century, editor, with related notes, drafts, submissions, and correspondence, undated, 1971, 1972 (Box 3)
      - American Reader, The: Twentieth Century, editor, with related notes, drafts, submissions, and correspondence, undated (Box 3)
      - Comics as Culture, (3 folders), undated (Box 3)
      - Studies In Bartleby the Scrivener: Annotated Checklist of Criticism, undated, 1977 (Box 3)
      - Studies In Bartleby the Scrivener: Correspondence, undated, 1970-1979 (Box 3)
      - Studies In Bartleby the Scrivener: Drafts, undated (Box 3)
      - Studies In Bartleby the Scrivener: Essays, undated, 1970, 1973, 1977 (Box 3)
      - Studies In Bartleby the Scrivener: Galley Proofs, undated (Box 3)
      - Studies In Bartleby the Scrivener: Merrill Studies Draft, undated (Box 3)
      - Studies In Bartleby the Scrivener: Related Research, undated, 1852, 1856,1953, 1970, 1972, 1975 (Box 3)
      - Studies In Bartleby the Scrivener: Reprint Information, undated, 1966, 1970-1973 (Box 3)
    - Other:
      - Charles Shultz Conversations, promotional postcard, 2000 (Box 3)
      - "Important Dates in the History of the American Comic Strip," undated (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous, undated, 1981 (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous Research Articles, undated (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous Research Capote, Truman: The Grass Harp, 1952 (Box 3)
      - Summary, "Introduction," 75 Years of the Comics, Maurice Horn (Box 3)
      - William Faulkner Bibliography/Biography, undated (Box 3)
      - William Faulkner's Light in August: an Annotated Checklist of Criticism, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Papers:
      - "The Appalachian Backgrounds of Billy De Beck's Snuffy Smith" for the Morris Harvey College Appalachian Festival, draft and illustrations included, undated, 1939, 1974, 1975 (Box 3)
      - "Hemingway in the Soviet Union," undated (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous School Papers, undated, 1954, 1955 (Box 3)
      - "Will the Real William Faulkner Please Stand Up?" undated (Box 3)
    - Reports:
      - Report to the Virginia Foundation for Humanities and Public Policies on "Images of the South," undated (Box 3)
    - Reviews:
      - Lanes, Selma C. The Art of Maurice Sendak, 1981 (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous Reviews, undated, 1978, 1980 (Box 3)
      - Readers Report, undated, 1977 (Box 3)
      - Various Richmond-Times Dispatch Sunday Book Reviews (Box 3)
      - "We Go Pogo," undated, 2002 (Box 3)
      - World Encyclopedia of Comics, The, undated, 1976, 1977 (Box 3)
      - Comics as Culture, undated, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Photocopy of camera pages, index, and related correspondence (Box 4)
      - Comics as Culture, undated (Box 4)
  - Sub-series C - Published and Unpublished Works by Others
    - Articles:
      - Berger, Arthur Asa: Various Articles, undated (Box 5)
      - Bollinger, Tom: "The New Zealand Comics Story," 1995 (Box 5)
      - Duncan, Bruce: Various Articles, undated (Box 5)
      - Duncan, Edgar Hill: "Tennyson: A Modern Appraisal," 1959 (Box 5)
      - Hagopian, John V.: "Bad Faith in The French Lieutenant's Woman," 1982 (Box 5)
      - Higgins, Brian and Steven Maillox: "Herman Melville, the Critical Reception," undated (Box 5)
      - Higgins, Jerry: "Creativity in Comic Strip Authors," 1967 (Box 5)
      - Holtsmark, Erling: "Popular Literature, Tarzan and the Classics," undated (Box 5)
      - Jowett, Garth S.: Various Articles, undated, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Marzio, Peter: "Politics and Christmas, Thomas Nast," 1975 (Box 5)
      - Mintz, Lawrence: "Formula, Fantasy, Realism and Propaganda in Milton Caniff's Comic Strips," 1974 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Book Reviews, undated, 1980 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Comics in the Classroom, undated (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Foreign Magazine Articles, undated, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Literary Articles, undated, 1972, 1980, 1981,1982 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Book Chapters, undated, 1956, 1984 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Comics Articles, undated, 1970, 1973, 1975-1978, 1980-1982, 1986-1988, 1995, 1996 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Children's Literature Articles, 1980, 1981 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Comic Articles, 1 of 2, undated (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Comic Articles, 2 of 2, undated, 1974, 1980, 1981, 1995 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Photocopied Film Guides, undated, 1975 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Popular Culture Articles, undated, 1975, 1976, 1977, 1978, 1979, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous Virginia Commonwealth University Articles (Box 5)
      - Mishkin, Daniel: "Pogo: Walt Kelly's American Dream," undated (Box 5)
      - Montgomery, Marion: "Richard Weaver Against the Establishment: an Essay Review," 1969 (Box 5)
      - Newspaper Comics Council, Inc., The, 1963 (Box 5)
      - Paperno, Slava and John V. Hagopian: "Official and Unofficial Responses to Nabokov in the Soviet Union," 1984 (Box 5)
      - Peek, George S.: "Beowulf and Grendel in Popular Culture: The Unmaking of a Hero," 1978 (Box 5)
      - Rickles, Milton: "Existential Themes in Beckett's "Unnamable," undated (Box 5)
    - Books:
      - Wills, Ridley and Allen Tate: The Golden Mean and Other Poems, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Comic Scripts:
      - Pekar, Harvey: Our Cancer Year, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Dissertations:
      - Winchester, Mark: Cartoon Theatricals from 1896 to 1927, (3 folders), 1995 (Box 5)
    - Manuscripts:
      - Beilke, Dr. Debra: Cracking Up the South: Humor and Identity in Southern Renaissance Literature, (3 folders), undated (Box 5)
      - Berger, Asa Arthur: How to Be Funny, undated, 1970 (Box 5)
      - Crawford's Encyclopedia of Comic Books, edited, (2 folders), undated (Box 5)
      - Hamlin, V. T.: The Man Who Walked with Dinosaurs(Alley Oop), 1984 (Box 5)
      - Harvey, R. C.: The Art of the Comics: An Aesthetic History of Comic Books, (4 folders), undated (Box 5)
      - Harvey, R. C.: Critiquing the Comics: An Armchair Guide to Daily Enjoyment/Appreciation of a Uniquely American Artform, undated (Box 6)
      - Harvey, R. C.: Critiquing the Comics: Fragments of an Aesthetic History of the Medium, (6 folders), 1993 (Box 6)
      - Harvey, R. C.: Meanwhile: The Life and Art of Milton Caniff, (20 folders), undated (Box 6)
      - Holtsmark, Erling B: Tarzan and Tradition: Classical Continuity in a Popular Type, (4 folders), undated (Box 6)
      - Vance, Michael: Forbidden Adventures: The History of the American Comics Groups,(3 folders), 1995 (Box 7)
    - Masters Thesis:
      - Ray, Frank Joe: Tennessee Writers: A Bibliographical Index, (3 folders), 1929 (Box 7)
    - Papers:
      - Barrier, Mike: "Writing A History of American Cartoons," 1977 (Box 7)
      - Barla, Orloff & Associates: "A Survey of Pulp Fiction," undated (Box 7)
      - Barla, Orloff & Associates: "Neil Simon: The Comedy King of Broadway," undated (Box 7)
      - "Biography, Roy Crane," undated (Box 7)
      - Brownell, Joseph: "Dreiser's American Tragedy: Fact and Fiction n Time, Place, and Character," 1978 (Box 7)
      - Cobb, Joseph: "Profiles in Humor," 1977 (Box 7)
      - Coleman, Earle: "The Funnies, the Movies, and Aesthetics," 1981 (Box 7)
      - Goldfield, David R.: "Modernization and the Southern Renaissance, 1920-1960," 1982 (Box 7)
      - Holm, Todd: "The Vilification of Kenneth Star," undated (Box 7)
      - Irving, Chris: "The Blue Beetle: a Definite Mystery Man, 1999 (Box 7)
      - Joyner, Nancy: "Michael Innes: "Finest of the Farceurs," undated (Box 7)
      - Lanyi, Ronlad Levitt: "Comic Books and Authority: An Interview with "Stainless Steve" Engleheart, edited draft, undated (Box 7)
      - MacFadden, Fred R.: "The Chocolate Thief," 1977 (Box 7)
      - Miscellaneous: American Film, undated (Box 7)
      - Miscellaneous: Literature, undated (Box 7)
      - Miscellaneous: Newspaper Comics, 1977 (Box 7)
      - Miscellaneous: Popular Culture, undated (Box 7)
      - Miscellaneous: Walt Disney, undated (Box 7)
      - Palumbo, Donald: "The Pattern of Allusions in Marvel Comics," undated (Box 7)
      - Sewell, Dorita: "Comics in Mexican Urbanization," 1978 (Box 7)
      - Strozier, Robert: "Television Comedy: Function and Structure," undated (Box 7)
      - Various: Papers collected commenting on the state of comics in America, undated ,1977 (Box 7)
      - Various: Papers presented at the Contemporary American Indian Literature Conference, undated, 1976 (Box 7)
      - Yacowar, M.: "Strategies of Structure in Some Comedies of Chaos," undated (Box 7)
    - Short Fiction: (Box 7)
      - Bebb, Bruce: "A Statue for Bugsy Segal," 1978 (Box 7)
    - Speeches: (Box 7)
      - Cole, Juan: Dedication Speech for Northwestern University Special Collections Comic Collection, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Richmond News Leader, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1973, 1974 (Box 8)
      Monday through Saturday
      1973: September 28
      October 6 - December 31
      1974: January 1 - February 2
      February 4 - 12
    - Richmond News Leader, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1974 (Box 9)
      1974: February 14 - March 23
    - Richmond News Leader, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages (Box 10)
      1974: March 25 - May 25
    - Richmond News Leader, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1974 (Box 11)
      1974: May 27 - September 7
    - Richmond News Leader, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1974, 1975 (Box 12)
      1974: September 9 - November 2
      November 4 - December 31
      1975: January 1 - 11
    - Richmond News Leader, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1975 (Box 13)
      1975: January 13 - April 7
    - Richmond News Leader, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1975 (Box 14)
      1975: April 8 - 12
      April 15 - July 11
    - Richmond News Leader, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1975 (Box 15)
      1975: July 11 - September 24
    - Richmond News Leader, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1975, 1976 (Box 16)
      Monday through Sunday
      1975: November 17 - December 31
      1976: January 1 - January 5
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1973, 1974 (Box 17)
      1973: September 3, September 5 - 14
      September 17 - 25
      September 27 - 29
      October 1
      October 3 - 17
      November 20
      November 22 - December 19
      December 21 - 31
      1974: January 1 - March 21
    - Richmond Times Dispatch, Black & White Daily Comic Strip Pages 1974, 1975 (Box 18)
      1974: March 23 - July 20
      July 23 - 31